{
    "subject": "resource/Preaortic_lymph_node",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#label",
    "object": "Preaortic lymph node",
    "human_readable": "The label of Preaortic lymph node is Preaortic lymph node.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9777204990386963,
            "question": "What is the label of a Preaortic lymph node?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8286766409873962,
            "question": "What is the function of a Preaortic lymph node?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8116051554679871,
            "question": "Where are Preaortic lymph nodes located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.796134352684021,
            "question": "Is 'Preaortic lymph node' a descriptive term for a specific type of lymph node?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6842404007911682,
            "question": "What is the significance of understanding the role of Preaortic lymph nodes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6836867332458496,
            "question": "Are there any diagnostic tests used to examine Preaortic lymph nodes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6815405488014221,
            "question": "How do Preaortic lymph nodes contribute to the immune system?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6690393686294556,
            "question": "What are some potential diseases or conditions that can affect Preaortic lymph nodes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6544140577316284,
            "question": "Are there other types of lymph nodes besides Preaortic lymph nodes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5086492896080017,
            "question": "How do doctors treat abnormalities in Preaortic lymph nodes?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The label of Preaortic lymph node is Preaortic lymph node.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5675_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there other types of lymph nodes besides Preaortic lymph nodes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5675_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some potential diseases or conditions that can affect Preaortic lymph nodes?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5675_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How do Preaortic lymph nodes contribute to the immune system?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5675_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5675_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5675_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5675_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5675_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5675_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5675_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5675_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5675_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5675_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5675_81.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text explicitly states \"The preaortic lymph nodes belong to the left lumbar chain of lymph nodes.\" and  \"Preaortic Lymph Nodes\". The description given in the document aligns with the statement that the label is \"Preaortic lymph node\".   \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided context information supports the statement that the label of Preaortic lymph nodes is indeed \"Preaortic lymph nodes,\" as this term is used multiple times throughout the documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}